Music
موسيقى
I can remember when we walked together
أستطيع أن أتذكر عندما مشينا معا
Sharing a love I thought would last forever
مشاركة الحب الذي اعتقدت أنه سيستمر إلى الأبد
Moonlight to show the way so we can follow
ضوء القمر ليبين لنا الطريق حتى نستطيع أن نتبعه
Waiting inside her eyes was my tomorrow
الانتظار داخل عينيها كان غدي
Then somethin' changed her mind, her kisses told me
أخبرتني قبلاتها أن شيئًا ما غير رأيها
I had no lovin' arms to hold me
لم يكن لدي أذرع محببة لتحملني
Every day I wake up, then I start to break up
كل يوم أستيقظ، ثم أبدأ في الانفصال
Lonely is a man without love
وحيد هو رجل بلا حب
Every day I start out, then I cry my heart out
كل يوم أبدأ، ثم أبكي من قلبي
Every day I wake up, then I start to break up
كل يوم أستيقظ، ثم أبدأ في الانفصال
Knowing that it's cloudy above
مع العلم أن الجو غائم في الأعلى
Every day I start out, then I cry my heart out
كل يوم أبدأ، ثم أبكي من قلبي
Lonely is a man without love
وحيد هو رجل بلا حب
I cannot face this world that's fallen down on me
لا أستطيع مواجهة هذا العالم الذي سقط علي
So, if you see my girl please send her home to me
لذا، إذا رأيت فتاتي من فضلك أرسلها إليّ في المنزل
Tell her about my heart that's slowly dying
أخبرها عن قلبي الذي يموت ببطء
Say I can't stop myself from crying
قل أنني لا أستطيع منع نفسي من البكاء
Every day I wake up, then I start to break up
كل يوم أستيقظ، ثم أبدأ في الانفصال
Lonely is a man without love
وحيد هو رجل بلا حب
Every day I start out, then I cry my heart out
كل يوم أبدأ، ثم أبكي من قلبي
Every day I wake up, then I start to break up
كل يوم أستيقظ، ثم أبدأ في الانفصال
Knowing that it's cloudy above
مع العلم أن الجو غائم في الأعلى
Every day I start out, then I cry my heart out
كل يوم أبدأ، ثم أبكي من قلبي
Lonely is a man without love
وحيد هو رجل بلا حب
Every day I wake up, then I start to break up
كل يوم أستيقظ، ثم أبدأ في الانفصال
Every day I start out, then I cry my heart out
كل يوم أبدأ، ثم أبكي من قلبي
Lonely is a man without love
وحيد هو رجل بلا حب